brickowl.com 2019-05-25

# Privacy Policy | Brick Owl - LEGO Marketplace

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Brick Owl collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [https://www.brickowl.com](https://www.brickowl.com/) website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Brick Owl.

**Data Controller**

Brick Owl processes personal data as a Controller as defined in GDPR. We process personal data to allow Users to place orders and interact with Brick Owl. All data collected by Brick Owl is stored securely in data centres located in the European Economic Area.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including when Users register on the site or place an order. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, Tax ID. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Brick Owl may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To improve customer service_  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _\- To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _\- To improve our Site_  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * _\- To process payments_  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * _\- To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature_  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _\- To help arbitrate disputes and preserve trust and safety_  
We retain and may inspect all messages sent through the Brick Owl messaging system.
  * _\- To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. It may be used to send catalog related emails It may be used to send notifications when items are added to your wishlist. 

We do not use the collected information to profile users or make automated decisions.

**Your access to information**

You have the right to request access to the information that we have on you, you can do so by visiting your user profile and exploring the various sections, or by contacting us.

**Information correction & deletion**

You can update any of the information that we have stored on you from your user profile, or you can contact us if you would like for your information to be deleted. Some information may need to be kept for financial record-keeping according to local government regulations.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with Google Analytics. We use a third party service provider to send mail on our behalf.

**Data Retention**

We only retain the Personal Data collected from a User for as long as the User’s account is active or otherwise for a limited period of time as long as we need it to fulfil the purposes for which we have initially collected it, unless otherwise required by law. 

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Brick Owl has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us. We are registered at Brick Owl Ltd, Kemp House, 160 City Road, London, EC1V 2NX. 

This document was last updated on May 9th, 2018
